<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<AlertExplanation>A nitralope has become dangerously bloated. You must relieve the pressure by milking it, or it may explode!</AlertExplanation>
	<AwaitingPrayersSacrifices>Awaiting prayers and sacrifices.</AwaitingPrayersSacrifices>
	<BringFog>Bring fog (18 mana)</BringFog>
	<BringRain>Bring rain (15 mana)</BringRain>
	<Charge>Charge: </Charge>
	<DangrouslyOverfull>Dangrously Overfull!</DangrouslyOverfull>
	<DevelopedRadiationSickness>{0} has developed radiation sickness</DevelopedRadiationSickness>
	<DiplomacyAwful>The flailing diplomatic "strategy" of {0} seemed chiefly to involve wild swings between aggression and panic, peppered liberally with lewd insults involving the negotiator for {1}'s antecedents. Your already strained relations have, understandably, worsened ({2} to relations).</DiplomacyAwful>
	<DiplomacyExcellent>{0}'s easy, but unyielding manner dealt well with a number of the negotiator for {1}'s concerns. Your relations have improved by {2}</DiplomacyExcellent>
	<DiplomacyMasterWorkLegendary>{0} made diplomacy look as easy as breathing, with an almost magical ability to make {1}'s negotiator see your perspective. Your relations have undergone a substantial improvement of {2}.</DiplomacyMasterWorkLegendary>
	<DiplomacyNormalGood>{0}'s negotiation adequately dealt with some minor disputes you have with {1}. Your relations have improved by {2}.</DiplomacyNormalGood>
	<DiplomacyPoor>The chief negotiation tactic employed by {0} seemed to be staring bored at the wall. This did little to diffuse tensions and engender a feeling of respect ({2} to relations))</DiplomacyPoor>
	<DispenseTrialCure>Dispense the trial cure</DispenseTrialCure>
	<EndExtremeWeather>End extreme weather (10 mana)</EndExtremeWeather>
	<EnteringRepairCycle>Entering Repair Cycle</EnteringRepairCycle>
	<ExplosiveRisk>Explosive risk!</ExplosiveRisk>
	<FilesPertanentLuciferiumCure>There seem to be files pertanent to a luciferium cure, but {0} lacks the intellectual skills to access them.</FilesPertanentLuciferiumCure>
	<FortunatelyDissipateAttack>Fortunately, {0} was able to dissipate the attack with their psychic capabilities.</FortunatelyDissipateAttack>
	<FortunatelyDissipateAttackShock>{0} was able to channel the attack, preventing harm to others, but is now in psychic shock!</FortunatelyDissipateAttackShock>
	<GoldenFoilPacket>A small, golden foil packet drops out of a nearby hatch!</GoldenFoilPacket>
	<GratefulSurvivorsAmazedDesc>The survivors of the crash are amazed by your rapid and professional emergency medical response, thanks to which no-one died. In gratitude, they have included a special system removed form the wreck.</GratefulSurvivorsAmazedDesc>
	<GratefulSurvivorsDesc>The survivors of the crash are very thankful for your help, and have send some supplies as a gesture of gratitude.</GratefulSurvivorsDesc>
	<HoloEmitterAreaFor>HoloEmitter area for {0}.</HoloEmitterAreaFor>
	<LargeMuffaloMigration>days!</LargeMuffaloMigration>
	<LinkGate>Link a gate.</LinkGate>
	<LinkGateDesc>Link this gate to another.</LinkGateDesc>
	<MalevolentPsychicDesc>{0} believes that a malevolent psychic energy is massing, and that this peaceful herd of muffalo are on the brink of a mass insanity.</MalevolentPsychicDesc>
	<MechanitesCureCorrupted>The mechanites in the cure have corrupted their programming and escaped their packaging!</MechanitesCureCorrupted>
	<MiscarriedRadiation>has miscarried due to radiation poisoning.</MiscarriedRadiation>
	<NegotiationsTrap>The negotiations are a trap!</NegotiationsTrap>
	<NewFaction>New Faction!</NewFaction>
	<NewFactionDesc>The survivors of the crash have decided to make a life for themselves here, and have founded a new faction</NewFactionDesc>
	<OnlyPsychicCanBroadcast>Only psychic pawns can broadcast a battle prayer</OnlyPsychicCanBroadcast>
	<OtherGateBuried>The other gate has been buried! We cannot transit!</OtherGateBuried>
	<Overfull>Overfull!</Overfull>
	<PlantDiedRatiation>A plant has died due to radiation damage</PlantDiedRatiation>
	<PsionicLandmine>A psionic landmine in the room generates a short-range psychic shock!</PsionicLandmine>
	<PsychicMessage>Psychic vision</PsychicMessage>
	<ReceivedVisionBattle>{PAWN_nameDef} has received visions accompanying the drone, showing a battle and crying out for help. Others must have noticed, so the site will probably be dangerous.</ReceivedVisionBattle>
	<ShootingStar>just saw something fall from the sky near here!</ShootingStar>
	<StargateLinked>Stargate linked to destination.</StargateLinked>
	<StargateNoEvidence>There is no evidence of a stargate there.</StargateNoEvidence>
	<StargateNotLinked>Stargate is not linked to a destination!</StargateNotLinked>
	<StrikeOurEnemies>Strike our enemies (40 mana)</StrikeOurEnemies>
	<Teleport>Teleport.</Teleport>
	<TeleportDesc>Teleport a person or animal.</TeleportDesc>
	<TeleporterLannotLockThickRock>Teleporter cannot lock on through the thick rock overhead!</TeleporterLannotLockThickRock>
	<ThinksResearchDubious>\n{0} thinks that the research is dubious, and is concerned that any remaining samples will be dangerous.</ThinksResearchDubious>
	<ThinksScienceUnderlying>\n{0} thinks that the science underlying the project is sound, and though the process has been lost, any remaining samples of the cure probably work.</ThinksScienceUnderlying>
	<YouCannotLock>You cannot lock onto anything there.</YouCannotLock>
	<YourCaravanSpottedMuffaloMigration>Your caravan has spotted a huge muffalo migration!</YourCaravanSpottedMuffaloMigration>
	<Mana>Mana</Mana>
	<Negotiate>Negotiate</Negotiate>
	<Social>Social</Social>
	<FormatOccupant>Format Occupant</FormatOccupant>
	<GratefulSurvivors>Grateful survivors</GratefulSurvivors>
	<LogOff>Log off {0}</LogOff>
	<ManhunterDanger>Manhunter danger</ManhunterDanger>
	<MuffaloMigration>Muffalo migration</MuffaloMigration>
	<ResurrectContained>Resurrect contained</ResurrectContained>
	<TransferToThisEmitter>Transfer to this emitter</TransferToThisEmitter>
	<TravelToTargetGate>Travel to target gate</TravelToTargetGate>
	<UseComputer>Use computer</UseComputer>
	<UsingComputer>Using computer</UsingComputer>
	<LetterLabelPawnsLostDueToMapCountdown>Left behind</LetterLabelPawnsLostDueToMapCountdown>
	<LetterPawnsLostDueToMapCountdown>Some of your animals or prisoners were left behind in the wilderness:\n\n{0}</LetterPawnsLostDueToMapCountdown>

</LanguageData>