<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Recon And Discovery</name>
  <author>SeveralPuffins</author>
  <targetVersion>0.17.1557</targetVersion>
  <description>
	Big risk, big reward! Recon and discovery adds new sites for your colonists to find.
	
		Crashed ships:      What will you find inside? A wealth of treasures? A crew in need of help?  A horde of flesh-eating chinchillas? All three!? Whatever it is, be quick, because you're not the only one who saw the ship come down.
		Lost labs:		    There's a rumour going around that luciferium addiction can be cured. Did the scientists here succeed?
		Ancient castles:    You finally pinpoint the source of a psychic drone. Is the technology to overcome death itself here on this planet?
		Abandoned colonies: Did anyone survive what happened here, and if so, are they quite human?
		
		
		Hi-tech rewards from missions: Read on to spoil the mysteries!
			Holo-emitters:   	   Scan HoloDisks to introduce holographic colonists of extraordinary talent to the team, or scan the brains of the recently dead to revive them holographically. Transfer a colonist instantly to a new emitter across the map! The convenience! the immortality! Just remember, they can't step out of range of their emitter ever again.
			Teleporters:     	   Slow to charge, but able to recover any living creature from anywhere on the planet.
			Deflectors:      	   Protect a small area of your colony from the effects of a solar flare.
			Gattling Lasers: 	   Built for space combat, these weapons will roast your enemies, and indeed anything else in between or within several yards. Just don't expect to recover much from the bodies, and be ready to fight the huge fire this will start.
			Devillo:		 	   Large, intelligent genetically engineered muffalo that secrete devilstrand into their wool. Their milk, devilcream, is also extraordinarily rich and nutritious.  
			Osiris Caskets:  	   An advanced Cryptosleep casket design, these caskets direct an army of luciferium nanites to restore health, reverse ageing and even to revive the recently dead, if at the cost of developing an addiction to the nanites. The power drain while active is extraordinary, so make sure you've got enough juice for your gothic experiments!  Also I can't, or more honestly don't want to, stop colonists from putting their dead cats in here.  
			Seraphites:      	   A self-replicating luciferium nanite. Could these little blue pills cure the worst cravings of your colonists?
  			Portable generators:   Need power on this trips away from home? Look no further! A low-output, long-lasting portable chemfuel generator, good for about 8 days usage. An ideal companion for camping mods (credit to DeadlyReg for his lovely chemfuel generator)!
			
  </description>
</ModMetaData>